(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ I get up in the evenin' ♪
♪ And I ain't got nothin' to say ♪
♪ I come home in the mornin' ♪
♪ I go to bed feelin' the same way ♪
♪ I ain't nothin' but tired ♪
♪ Man, I'm just tired
and bored with myself ♪
♪ Hey there, baby ♪
♪ I could use just a little help ♪
♪ You can't start a fire ♪
♪ You can't start a fire without a spark ♪
♪ This gun's for hire ♪
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ Messages keeps gettin' clearer ♪
♪ Radio's on and I'm
movin' 'round my place ♪
♪ I check my look in the mirror ♪
♪ Wanna change my clothes,
my hair, my face ♪
♪ Man, I ain't gettin' nowhere ♪
♪ I'm just livin' in a dump like this ♪
♪ There's somethin' happenin' somewhere ♪
♪ Baby, I just know that there is ♪
♪ You can't start a fire ♪
♪ You can't start a fire without a spark ♪
♪ This gun's for hire ♪
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ You sit around gettin' older ♪
♪ There's a joke here
somewhere and it's on me ♪
♪ I'll shake this world off my shoulders ♪
♪ Come on, baby, the laugh's on me ♪
♪ Stay on the streets of this town ♪
♪ And they'll be carvin' you up alright ♪
♪ They say you gotta stay hungry ♪
♪ Hey baby, I'm just
about starvin' tonight ♪
♪ I'm dyin' for some action ♪
♪ I'm sick of sittin' 'round
here tryin' to write this book ♪
♪ I need a love reaction ♪
♪ Come on now, baby, gimme just one look ♪
♪ You can't start a fire ♪
♪ Sittin' 'round cryin'
over a broken heart ♪
♪ This gun's for hire ♪
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
♪ You can't start a fire ♪
♪ Worryin' about your
little world fallin' apart ♪
♪ This gun's for hire ♪
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ Even if we're just dancin' in the dark ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)
♪ Hey, baby ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience cheering)